{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Specialty \u0026 Texture Painters","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/40366/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40366,"taskName":"Specialty Painting - Textures","taskDescription":"Apply Textured Paint Finishes","xmTaskDescriptor":"Specialty \u0026 Texture Painters","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":125,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"painters Specialty Textures custom finish","textMessagingName":"Textured Paint","rolloverLongDesc":"Rollers, brushes or trowels are used to shape patterns into a specially thickened paint to create a variety of decorative patterns. Note separate categories for popcorn finishes \u0026 genuine stucco.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes rolled, brushed or troweled on finishes.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Apply Textured Paint Finishes.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Textured Painting \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Re-texture or Paint Texture on Walls, Ceilings","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":55,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Specialty Texture Painting","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Specialty Painting - Textures","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Texture Painting Project","urlName":"Specialty-Painting-Textures","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Textured Painting Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"painters,Specialty,Textures,custom,finish,finishes,decorative,jobs,paint,wall,porch,stain,Woodstock","emcCategoryOid":-12054,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":660,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40366/":{"taskOID":40366,"originalTaskOID":40366,"setID":660,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5223,"questionDisplayText":"Texture needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of texturing do you need? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":824,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Apply texture to unfinished drywall for paint","answerDisplayText":"Apply texture to unfinished drywall for paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3776,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Match new drywall to existing walls/ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Match new drywall to existing walls/ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5232,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair/Patch drywall","answerDisplayText":"Repair/Patch drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4895,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Prepare for wallpaper/special finish","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for wallpaper/special finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5176,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Remove popcorn acoustic ceiling spray","answerDisplayText":"Remove popcorn acoustic ceiling spray","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1716,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Create faux effect","answerDisplayText":"Create faux effect","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4543,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Paint also needed","answerDisplayText":"Paint also needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5404,"questionDisplayText":"Surface","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What surfaces need to be textured?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6766,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wall(s)","answerDisplayText":"Wall(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1302,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ceiling(s)","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5223,"questionDisplayText":"Texture needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of texturing do you need? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":824,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Apply texture to unfinished drywall for paint","answerDisplayText":"Apply texture to unfinished drywall for paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3776,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Match new drywall to existing walls/ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Match new drywall to existing walls/ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5232,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair/Patch drywall","answerDisplayText":"Repair/Patch drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4895,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Prepare for wallpaper/special finish","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for wallpaper/special finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5176,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Remove popcorn acoustic ceiling spray","answerDisplayText":"Remove popcorn acoustic ceiling spray","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1716,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Create faux effect","answerDisplayText":"Create faux effect","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4543,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Paint also needed","answerDisplayText":"Paint also needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":824,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Apply texture to unfinished drywall for paint","answerDisplayText":"Apply texture to unfinished drywall for paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3776,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Match new drywall to existing walls/ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Match new drywall to existing walls/ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5232,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair/Patch drywall","answerDisplayText":"Repair/Patch drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4895,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Prepare for wallpaper/special finish","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for wallpaper/special finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5176,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Remove popcorn acoustic ceiling spray","answerDisplayText":"Remove popcorn acoustic ceiling spray","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1716,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Create faux effect","answerDisplayText":"Create faux effect","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4543,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Paint also needed","answerDisplayText":"Paint also needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5404,"questionDisplayText":"Surface","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What surfaces need to be textured?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6766,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wall(s)","answerDisplayText":"Wall(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1302,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ceiling(s)","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6766,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wall(s)","answerDisplayText":"Wall(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1302,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Ceiling(s)","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}